(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is allowed.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK
2次販売グッズ
2nd Batch Merchandise Sales
だから
So!
君のこと
I love you...
大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
...love you, love you, love you, love you, love you!
溢れるこの想い
These overflowing feelings
たくさんの素敵なショート動画ありがとうございます！
Thank you for the many wonderful short videos!
きっと
Surely
もっと止まらない
will not stop anymore!
Ai ai ai ai I love you
素敵なショート動画ありがとうございました！
Thank you for the wonderful short videos!
Ai ai ai ai I need you
もっと！
More!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
夢見るハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming heart goes pyon pyon pyon.
穴に落ちてあみゃみゃみゃ
Falling in a hole, amya mya mya.
こんなになっても未だ抜け出せない
Even like this, I still can't get out.
どうしたものかなヌイヌイヌイ
What should I do, nui nui nui.
助けて君たちアホイホイ
Save me everyone, ahoy hoi.
もっともっともっと
More, more, more!
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you like.
アニメにハマって
I got hooked on anime,
歌いたくなっちゃった
and now I want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら
Watching scenes of my favs,
カラオケ歌えるなんて...
being able to sing karaoke to them...
尊すぎてツラいっ！
It's so precious it hurts!
歌いたい曲、見つけよう！
Let's find the songs we want to sing!
JOYSOUND！
JOYSOUND!
ホロライブ3期生、プライズ順次展開中！
Hololive 3rd Gen prizes are rolling out now!
パペットぬいぐるみ
Puppet Plushies
寝そべりミニマスコット
Laying Down Mini Mascots
大判マウスパッド
Large Mousepads
全国のアミューズメント施設でGETしてね！
Get them at amusement centers nationwide!
吉野家で
At Yoshinoya,
ごはんしよ♪
let's have a meal.
ぎゅっ
Gyu (Beef)
ぎゅっぎゅ
Gyu gyu
ん～
Mmm~
ぎゅっ
Gyu
うまっ
Delicious.
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Taste the seriousness of the originator.
牛丼は吉野家。
Beef bowls are Yoshinoya.
今日も、吉野家日和です。
Today is another perfect day for Yoshinoya.
やっぱこれなあ
It's gotta be this.
ホロライブ3期生ミニCDコレクション
Hololive 3rd Generation Mini CD Collection
ガシャポンに登場！
Appearing in Gashapon!
ガシャポン！
Gashapon!
せーの
Ready...
本日はhololive 3rd Generation Live
Today, at hololive 3rd Generation Live...
きゅるるん大作戦
"Kyururun Great Strategy"
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
~The Ultimate Idols, You Have No Choice But To Stan~
にご来場いただき
...thank you for coming...
ここまできたら...
Now that you're here...
ライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live, I have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and the use of recording equipment are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue.
喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は...
If you happen to feel unwell...
...無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
...please do not push yourself and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ...
Moshing, diving inside the venue...
...ステージに物を投げ込むなど...
...throwing objects onto the stage...
...他の迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は...
...or any behavior that causes trouble or interferes with the show...
...一切禁止です。
...is strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
はーい！
Okaaay!
また、本公演は映像配信及び、写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り...
Also, video streaming and photography cameras will be inside the venue...
...客席が映り込む場合があります。
...and the audience may be captured in the shots.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能が...
These videos and photos may be used for promotion...
...可能性がありますので...
...there is a possibility they will be used, so...
笑わないで！
Don't laugh!
予めご了承ください。
Please be aware of this in advance.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは、#きゅるるん大作戦 DAY1 です。
Also, the live hashtag is #KyururunDaisakusen DAY1.
ハッシュタグを使って、たくさん盛り上げてくれると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you use the hashtag to hype it up a lot!
それでは、開演までもう少しです。
Now then, it's just a little longer until the start.
みんなの声をたくさん聞かせてぺこー！
Let me hear everyone's voices, Peko!
それじゃあ3期生！
Alright then, 3rd Gen!
円陣いくかー！
Let's do the circle cheer!
みんな、今からマイクが無くなるので、静かに...静かに...
Everyone, the mic is going away now, so be quiet... be quiet...
I I I I I love you
もう I I I I I need you
Geez, I I I I I need you
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I like.
3期生ライブ、いくぺこ！
3rd Gen Live, here we go peko!
みんなで最高の思い出、作ろうね！
Let's make the best memories together!
くるくる脳内君だらけ
My brain is spinning, full of you.
どうかしてるわね私
I must be losing my mind.
心臓ドキドキ鳴ってる
My heart is pounding.
警報
Warning.
毎日幻覚現れて
Hallucinations appear every day.
頭に花咲いちゃって
Flowers are blooming in my head.
こういった奴は非常識ですわ
This kind of thing is against common sense.
いっそ食べちゃいたい
I'd rather just eat you up.
フリーズした感情
Frozen emotions.
誰もが持ってる願い
A wish that everyone holds.
純純純盲詠唱
Chanting for pure, pure, blind love.
堂々して急上昇
Magnificently soaring.
これが恋ならもう後悔しないわ
If this is love, I won't regret it anymore.
だから
So,
君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you.
溢れるこの
This overflowing...
愛は
Love is...
ずってもっと止まらない
Never stopping, it just grows.
I I I I I love you
君が I I I I I need you
You... I I I I I need you
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you like.
ゆるゆるハートがピョンピョンピョン
My loose heart goes hop hop hop!
罠に落ちてアビャアビャ
Falling into a trap, abya abya!
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
I've become like this, but I still can't escape.
どうしたもんかねヌイヌイヌイ
What should I do, nui nui nui?
助けて君たちアホイホイ
Save me, you guys, ahoy-hoy!
もっと もっと
More, more...
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you like.
ふわふわ浮かぶ夢の中
Floating lightly inside a dream.
君の声で目が覚めた
I woke up at the sound of your voice.
五感全部が君でおかしくなる
All five senses go crazy because of you.
毎度お騒がせごめん
Sorry for the disturbance every time.
キュンで壊れちゃいそうだ
I feel like I'm going to break from the love.
こういった奴は制御不能ですわ
This kind of thing is uncontrollable.
いっそ抱きしめて
Just hold me tight already.
壊してもいいよ
You can break me if you want.
誰にも邪魔はさせない
I won't let anyone get in the way.
ピチピチ感情で
With fresh and lively emotions,
キラキラ急展開
A sparkling sudden turn of events.
これが運命ならもう迷わない
If this is fate, I won't hesitate anymore.
覚悟してね
Brace yourself, okay?
君だけが大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
I love only you, love you, love you, love you, love you.
私のこの
This love of mine,
愛は
Love is...
ずっともう離さない
Will never let you go.
Be be be my baby and...
Kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss to me
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
私だけを見ててね
Look only at me, okay?
無視したろは泣いちゃうかもね
If you ignore me, I might just cry.
だってそんなのってないぺこちゃん
Because that's just impossible, Peko-chan!
わかってるよねダーリン
You understand, right, darling?
いっぱい愛を待ってます
I'm waiting for lots of love!
ノエルもっと！
Noel, more!
ぺこらもっと！
Pekora, more!
フレアもっと！
Flare, more!
マリンもっと！
Marine, more!
ホロライブファンタジーを...
Hololive Fantasy...
愛してるー！
We love you!
君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much!
溢れるこの愛は
This overflowing love...
ずっとまとまらない
will never settle down forever.
愛愛愛愛 I love you
Love, love, love, love, I love you,
君が愛愛愛愛 I need you
you are love, love, love, love, I need you.
もっと！
More!
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want.
ときめくハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My throbbing heart goes pyon pyon pyon.
矢に打たれておびょびょ
Struck by an arrow, oh my!
こんなになったら魔法は解けましん
If it comes to this, the magic won't break.
本気になってるヌイヌイヌイ
I'm getting serious, nui nui nui.
行ってますそこまでアホイホイ
I'm coming over there, ahoy hoi!
もっと！
More!
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you like, okay?
愛愛愛愛 I love you
Love, love, love, love, I love you.
愛愛愛愛 I need you
Love, love, love, love, I need you.
愛愛愛愛 I love you
Love, love, love, love, I love you.
愛愛愛愛 I need you
Love, love, love, love, I need you.
私達の愛をもっと！
Take more of our love!
安乗ピチピチ AHOY！
Safe sailing, splash splash, AHOY!
ピカチュキ？ AHOY！
Sparkling kiss? AHOY!
お色気担当マリンです
I'm the one in charge of sex appeal, Marine!
踊るアホイに見るアホイ
The dancing fool and the watching fool.
共に踊らにゃ損に決まりましゅ
You definitely lose out if you don't dance along.
お尻！
Butt!
船長だろ！
It's the Captain!
野うさぎ同盟 参加独走
Nousagi Alliance, joining the solo race.
最強女神ぺこだ
I'm the strongest goddess, Peko!
ママ！
Mama!
よしよしして！
Pat my head!
バブー！
Babuu!
ちょっと！横取りめ！
Hey! You thief!
ペイペイペイ！
Pei pei pei!
ウサギか？
Are you a rabbit?
大成功のため！
For the sake of huge success!
初見コールもいけちゃう？
Can you do the call even if it's your first time?
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru Idol.
実家の安心感コルル
Giving you that sense of safety like home.
お決まりのファンサで好き溢れちゃう
Love overflows with the standard fanservice.
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru Idol.
極めたオタ芸踊るる
Dancing the wotagei we've mastered.
新規もいる？
Any newcomers here?
古参いる？
Any veterans here?
もはや息が阿吽の呼吸ってじゃん
Our breathing is already in perfect harmony.
会いたい！
Want to meet!
推したい！
Want to support!
現場で
At the venue...
全力応援 きゅるきゅる
supporting with all our might, kyuru kyuru!
ちあ！ちあ！
Cheer! Cheer!
フレフレ エルフレ
Hooray hooray, Elfriends!
褒められて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type who grows when praised.
ダーリン？
Darling?
はいハニー？
Yes, honey?
世界で一番愛してる！
I love you the most in the world!
今ならチャンネル登録なんと無料！
Subscribe now and it's actually free!
JOY JOY ENJOY 団長のノエルです
Joy joy enjoy, it's the Captain, Noel!
ゆるふわ脳筋 お待ちかねだよ
The fluffy muscle-brain you've been waiting for.
朗読みたい？
Want a reading?
ラップでいたい？
Want to be in a rap?
牛丼！並盛！つゆだくの大魔神
Beef bowl! Regular size! The sauce-drenched giant god!
ガチ恋距離 追い越う 和響
Let's cross the gachikoi distance and make some noise!
ある？
Is there?
実質？
Effectively?
メンバー？
A member?
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru Idol.
ハートの振付もコピルル
Copying the heart choreography too.
可愛とか超えて好きこじらせちゃう
Going beyond cute, making this love complicated.
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru Idol.
概念からも集める
Gathering even from concepts.
ガチ勢も
Die-hard fans too,
遠征も
expedition fans too,
もはや全員同士って決定じゃん
it's already decided we're all comrades.
行きたい！
Want to go!
寄りたい！
Want to stop by!
現場で
At the venue...
全通応援 きゅるきゅる
attending every show and cheering, kyuru kyuru!
ちあ！ちあ！
Cheer! Cheer!
みんなの王様！
Everyone's King!
みんなの歌姫！
Everyone's Songstress!
みんなの団長！
Everyone's Captain!
みんなの船長！
Love and Peace
泣く日も 推しがへこんだ時でも
even on days you cry, or when your oshi is feeling down.
Try あのエラー 重ねた
Try, having piled up those errors,
君と見たい景色があるんだ
there's a scenery I want to see with you.
うっしゃーいくぞ！
Alright, let's go!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru Idol.
実家の安心感コルル
Giving you that sense of safety like home.
お決まりのファンサで
With the standard fanservice...
好き！
Like!
大好き！
Love!
一生好きだよ！
I'll love you for my whole life!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru Idol.
ラストまで追いかけるる
Chasing you until the very end.
概念が尊
The concept is precious,
存在が最強 大優勝
the existence is the strongest, huge victory!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru Idol.
永遠の愛誓えるる
I can pledge eternal love.
単推しも
Single-oshi fans,
箱推しも
box-oshi fans too,
もはや生涯オタク決定じゃん
it's decided you're an otaku for life.
もうずっと！
Forever!
現場で
At the venue...
限界応援 きゅるきゅる
limit-breaking support, kyuru kyuru!
うー、はい！ちゅ！
Ooh, yes! Chu!
一生懸命シェア！
Doing our best to share!
あー！
Ah!
みんな...！
Everyone...!
ちょっと乱心しすぎた...
We went a bit too crazy...
ちょっと落ち着こう。
Let's calm down a bit.
落ち着くために自己紹介しよう、ここで。
Let's introduce ourselves to calm down.
自己紹介？オッケー。
Self-intros? Okay.
そうだね。
That sounds good.
ぺこーらから行きますよー！
Pekora will start!
はい！
Yes!
こんぺここんぺここんぺこー！
Konpeko Konpeko Konpeko!
ホロライブ3期生の兎田ぺこらと...
Hololive 3rd Gen's Usada Pekora and...
お前、「こんぺこ」って言わしてやれよ。
Hey, let them say "Konpeko".
言いたかった？確かに。
Did you want to say it? True.
もう一回やってよ。
Do it one more time.
なんて言えばいいの、ぺこらはじゃあ？
What should Pekora say then?
「こんぺここんぺここんぺこ」っつったら...
If you say "Konpeko Konpeko Konpeko"...
向こうも言いたいんだって。
...they want to say it too.
あ、そういうことね！
Ah, that's what you mean!
みんな言ってくれますかー？
Will everyone say it for me?
やった！
Yay!
じゃあ行きますよー！
Here we go then!
こんぺここんぺここんぺこー！
Konpeko Konpeko Konpeko!
いいよー！
Nice!
ホロライブ3期生の...
Hololive 3rd Gen's...
兎田ぺこらと！
Usada Pekora and!
はい、じゃあフレアは「こんぬい」じゃなくて...
Okay, so for Flare, instead of "Kon-nui"...
「はい、ダーリン」って言うから、「はい、ハニー」って返してください。
I'll say "Hi, Darlin'", so please reply with "Hi, Honey".
はい！
Okay!
いくよー！
Here I go!
はい、ダーリン！
Hi, Darlin'!
（はい、ハニー！）
(Hi, Honey!)
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ホロライブ3期生の不知火フレアと？
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shiranui Flare and?
と？
And?
はい、じゃあ団長は...
Okay, then for Danchou...
えー、「牛丼は？」って言うんで、「並盛！」って言ってください。
Umm, I'll say "How about Gyudon?", so please say "Regular size!".
並！？
Regular!?
大盛りでいいんじゃない？
Shouldn't it be large size?
並盛だから！
It's regular size!
じゃあ行くよー！
Alright, here I go!
牛丼は？
How about Gyudon?
（並盛ー！）
(Regular size!)
イェーイ！そうだよね！
Yay! That's right!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルと！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shirogane Noel and!
と？
And?
君たち！
You guys!
今、もしかして...
Just now, did you possibly...
フレアのことハニーって言った！？
...call Flare "Honey"!?
言ってた！言ってた！
They did! They did!
言ってたよ！
They definitely said it!
違う！
No!
よろよろ...
*Stagger*...
何のこと！？
What are you talking about!?
何のことか忘れてしまった！
I've forgotten all about it!
君たち！
You guys!
なんちゃって！
Just kidding!
え、じゃあ...どうしよっかな。
Umm, so... what should I do?
あ、じゃあ普通に「Ahoy」で行きますんで、「Ahoy」って言ってくださいね。
Ah, I'll just go with "Ahoy", so please say "Ahoy" back.
はーい。
Okaay.
Ahoy！！
Ahoy!!
（Ahoy！！）
(Ahoy!!)
誰がアホや！
Who are you calling an idiot!
なんちゃって。
Just kidding.
えー、ホロライブ3期生...
Umm, Hololive 3rd Gen...
えーっと...出ない、出ない。
Uhhh... I can't get it out.
ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の...
Hololive 3rd Gen, Captain of the Houshou Pirates...
宝鐘マリンです！
Houshou Marine!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
やっとさ...
Finally...
みんななんか、アイドル口上みたいなの...
Since everyone has an idol slogan...
できたやつはやる？やらん？
Should we do the ones we made? Or not?
やろうよ！
Let's do it!
これはやるしかなくない？
We have to do this, right?
そう、配信でやった...
Right, the ones we did on stream...
また順番で。
In order again.
あ、順番で行きましょう、順番で。
Ah, let's go in order.
みんな覚えてるよね？ぺこらの口上！
Everyone remembers, right? Pekora's slogan!
絶対覚えてねえぞ！
I bet they don't remember!
覚えてるよね...？ちゃんと、よろしく頼むよー！
You remember right...? I'm counting on you!
覚えてる人、手挙げてー！
Raise your hand if you remember!
めっちゃ手が上がってるね。
So many hands are going up.
全然上がってないよ！
Not at all!
全然覚えてねえって！
They don't remember at all!
じゃあ、ま、今から覚えてくださいね。
Well, please learn it now.
じゃあぺこらから行きますよー！
Pekora's starting now!
ラビットキャロットキラっと登場！
Rabbit, Carrot, sparkling entrance!
最強アイドルぺこらが来たぺこー！
Strongest Idol Pekora has arrived-peko!
まだまだ続くよー！
It's not over yet!
ぺこら！スターリー！
Pekora! Starry!
めっちゃキラキラしてる！
So sparkly!
ちょっと...フレアめっちゃ難しいんだけどさ...
Wait... Flare's is super difficult...
いけるかな、みんな。
Can everyone do it?
いけるいける！
They can do it!
団長たちも、あの、聞こえるから大丈夫だよ！
We're listening too, so it's fine!
これ、あの、みんなにもコール＆レスポンスして欲しくて。
I want everyone to join the call and response.
あの、「準備は？」って言ったら「万端！」。
When I say "Ready?", say "All set!".
万端！
All set!
「コールは？」って聞くので「簡単！」。
I'll ask "Call is?", so say "Easy!".
簡単！
Easy!
で、手拍子！パンパン！
Then, clap! Clap clap!
パンパン！
Clap clap!
ステップ！タンタン！
Step! Tap tap!
タンタン！
Tap tap!
私は？ふーたん！
Who am I? Fu-tan!
ふーたん！
Fu-tan!
めっちゃ難しいやん！
That's super hard!
これ練習ね。
That was practice.
覚えてください！
Please memorize it!
では、いきますよ！
Alright, here we go!
こんぬい！
Kon-nui!
準備はー？
Readyー?
（万端ー！）
(All setー!)
コールはー？
Call isー?
（簡単ー！）
(Easyー!)
手拍子！
Clap!
（パンパン！）
(Clap clap!)
ステップ！
Step!
（タンタン！）
(Tap tap!)
私はー？
Who am Iー?
（ふーたん！）
(Fu-tan!)
ホロライブ3期生、不知火フレアです！
Hololive 3rd Gen, Shiranui Flare!
おぉー！すごい！
Ooh! Amazing!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
難しいのにすごいですよ！
It's hard but you guys are great!
じゃあ次はノエル！
Next is Noel!
ノエル行きます！
Noel's going!
団長のコール＆レスポンス、なんかラップします！
Danchou's call and response is... I'm gonna rap!
こっから行こうかな。
I guess I'll start here.
行きます！
Here I go!
好きな質問、至高の食べ物！
Favorite question, supreme food!
牛丼！並盛！飲み物！？
Gyudon! Regular size! Drink!?
みんなの求婚、だめだめ重婚！
Everyone's proposal, no no bigamy!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルでーす！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shirogane Noel!
練習しましょう。
Let's practice.
マリンが「マリンは？」って言ったら、
If Marine says "Marine is?",
君たちは「船長！」
You guys say "Captain!".
で、マリンが「君らは？」って言ったら
Then, if Marine says "You guys are?",
「一味！」
"Crew!".
我ら無敵の
We are the invincible...
「海賊団！」
"Pirate Crew!".
で、最後に「宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです」って言うから
And finally, I'll say "Houshou Pirate Crew Captain, Houshou Marine",
そしたら問答無用で「かわいい！」って言う。
then you must say "Cute!" without question.
分かりましたね？
Understood?
ま、余裕だよね。
Well, it's easy, right?
はい、素晴らしいお返事できて、まる。
Yes, wonderful reply, full marks.
じゃあ行きますよ！
Okay, here we go!
マリンは？
Marine is?
船長！
Captain!
君らは？
You guys are?
一味！
Crew!
我ら無敵の？
We are the invincible?
海賊団！
Pirate Crew!
宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです！
Houshou Pirate Crew Captain, Houshou Marine!
かわいい！
Cute!
いや〜気持ちいいんだよこれが。
Man, this feels good.
そんなかわいい？
That cute?
良かったな、かわいいって言われて。
Good for you, being called cute.
そんなことないけど...
Not really, but...
すごい良い。
It's great.
え、でもコールアンドレスポンスね、ちょっと一発目からもうすごい難しいのやらせちゃってどうもすみませんね。
But sorry for making you do such a difficult call-and-response right from the start.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
え、声が聞こえますよ！
Eh, I can hear your voices!
さっきのさ、うちらの円陣聞こえました？
Did you hear our huddle cheer earlier?
聞こえた！
We heard it!
嬉しい！
I'm happy!
ちょっと何か聞こえるかなって不安だったんだよね。
We were a bit worried if you could hear it.
こっちにはね、君らの声よく聞こえるんだけど。
We can hear your voices well over here, though.
流石にマイク介さないとちっちゃかったかなと思って。
I thought it might be too quiet without the mic.
お腹から出した。
We projected from our stomachs.
あ、聞こえた？
Ah, you heard it?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
聞こえるよ！
We can hear you!
こっちにも声聞こえてますよ！
Your voices are reaching us here too!
あ、衣装のことも言わなきゃ。
Ah, I have to mention the costumes too.
そうだよ！
That's right!
でもかわいい！
But cute!
突然の新衣装！
Sudden new costumes!
かわいいでしょ？
Cute, right?
ちょっとずつ違うところがね、ありますんで。
There are slight differences for each of us.
ペコラはみみみ！
Pekora has mimimi (ears)!
輪っかが付いているペコね！
There's a halo attached-peko!
なんと！発案者はノエちゃん！
Surprisingly! The idea came from Noe-chan!
そう、ノエル。
Yeah, Noel.
すごいでしょ。
Amazing, right?
マリンはね、ヘッドドレスがね、ほらこんな感じで。
Marine's head dress is, look, like this.
バツバツバツバツバツ。
X X X X X.
かわいい！
Cute!
団長は、なんかポンポン付いてます。
The Captain has pom-poms attached.
かわいい！
Cute!
フレアは、この頭のリボンかな？
For Flare, maybe this ribbon on the head?
かわいいね。
So cute.
あとニーソ違いますね。
Also the knee socks are different.
フレアはギャルじゃないんでね。
Flare isn't a gyaru, so.
あたしらギャル。
We are gyarus.
ペコラもギャル。
Pekora is also a gyaru.
ギャルでーす。
I'm a gyaru.
皆さん、あの、うちらね結構めちゃめちゃ喋りすぎてるみたいで。
Everyone, um, it seems we've been talking way too much.
やばいやばい！
Oh no!
音楽しないのかい？みたいな。
Like, "Aren't you going to do music?"
スタッフさんが...
The staff is...
ちなみに配信で見てる方、Youtubeで見てる方、
By the way, those watching the stream or on YouTube,
概要欄にね、配信チケットのリンクありますので是非。
there is a link for the stream ticket in the description, so please.
次の曲でちょっとチラ見せは...
The preview will end with the next song...
終わっちゃうので今のうちに！
It's going to end, so check it now!
見て欲しいパートがいっぱいあるんで。
There are lots of parts we want you to see.
お願いします！
Please!
ハッシュタグきゅるるん大作戦Day1でいっぱい呟いてね！
Please tweet a lot with hashtag Kyururun Daisakusen Day 1!
ていうか、それもやらないと。あのね、生バンドがね
By the way, we have to do that too. You know, the live band,
すごいかっこいいじゃない？
is super cool, right?
だからちょっと聴かしたくて。じゃあペコラちゃんからいってもらっていいですか？
So I wanted to let you hear it. Can you start, Pekora-chan?
了解！エアバンド、キーボード担当！兎田ペコラ！
Roger! Air band, on Keyboard! Usada Pekora!
いくよ！ギター！宝鐘マリン！
Let's go! Guitar! Houshou Marine!
はい、ドラム！白銀ノエル！
Yes, Drums! Shirogane Noel!
じゃあフレア、ベースやります！
Then Flare, I'll do bass!
あ〜んかっこいいわ！
Ah, so cool!
はい、うちらが演奏してます。
Yes, we are playing it.
じゃあそろそろ次の曲いきましょうか。
Well then, shall we move to the next song?
はい、じゃあそろそろ次の曲いきましょう。
Okay, let's go to the next song.
Reality Fantasy!
H-O-L-O-L-I-V-E
F-A-N-T-A-S-Y
冒険出発さ
Adventure, departure!
挑戦開始さ
Challenge, start!
さあ！冒険出発さ
Come on! Adventure, departure!
挑戦開始さ さあ！
Challenge, start, come on!
冒険出発さ
Adventure, departure!
挑戦開始さ さあ！
Challenge, start, come on!
お宝探しに
Searching for treasure,
大海原いざ出航だ
Into the vast ocean, setting sail!
冒険！出発！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Come on!
挑戦！開始！さあ！
Challenge! Start! Come on!
身も心もぴょんぴょん
Body and soul, hop-hop!
わくわく 頂点上々
Excitement reaching the very top!
冒険！出発！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Come on!
挑戦！開始！さあ！
Challenge! Start! Come on!
水平線向こう側
Beyond the horizon,
新天地待っててね
Wait for us, new world!
運命なんか飛び越えて
Leaping right over fate,
その先へ
To what lies ahead!
さあ リアリティ
Come on, Reality,
ファンタジー
Fantasy,
二つの狭間へ
Into the gap between the two!
夢歌え 声高く
Sing your dreams, loud and clear,
一緒に さあ
Together, come on!
まだ見ぬ世界へと
To a world yet unseen,
キミを連れてくよ
We'll take you there!
みんなが繋がる
A story where everyone connects,
物語 さあ始まるよ
It's starting now!
冒険！出発！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Come on!
挑戦！開始！さあ！
Challenge! Start! Come on!
冒険！出発！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Come on!
挑戦！開始！さあ！
Challenge! Start! Come on!
みんなの志 いだき
Embracing everyone's ambitions,
いざ騎士団集合！
Knights, assemble!
冒険！出発！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Come on!
挑戦！開始！さあ！
Challenge! Start! Come on!
胸に宿る太陽
With the sun in my heart,
風を切って さらに輝け
Cut through the wind and shine brighter!
冒険！出発！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Come on!
挑戦！開始！さあ！
Challenge! Start! Come on!
名誉と夢
Honor and dreams,
晴天に掲げたら
Hoisted high in the clear sky,
突撃だー！
Charge!
ヨーソロー！
Aye aye!
妖精たち
Fairies,
この旅 見守って
Watch over this journey!
さあ リアリティ
Come on, Reality,
ファンタジー
Fantasy,
二つの狭間へ
Into the gap between the two!
声上げて 歌え
Raise your voice and sing,
ユートピアへ さあ
To Utopia, come on!
それぞれの世界から
From each of our worlds,
垣根を越えたら
If we cross the fences,
みんなが繋がる
A story where everyone connects,
物語 さあ始まるよ
It's starting now!
明るく陽気に 荒波乗り越え
Bright and cheerful, riding the rough waves!
ホロ ライブ！
Holo- Live!
愛嬌開放 うさ耳澄まして
Charm unleashed, perk up those bunny ears!
ホロ ライブ！
Holo- Live!
騎士道と誇り 胸に刻んだら
With chivalry and pride carved in my heart!
ホロ ライブ！
Holo- Live!
神話に伝わる 神秘の囁き
The mysterious whispers of myths!
ホロ ライブ！
Holo- Live!
冒険！出発！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Come on!
挑戦！開始！さあ！
Challenge! Start! Come on!
さあ リアリティ
Come on, Reality,
ファンタジー
Fantasy,
二つの狭間へ
Into the gap between the two!
夢歌え 声高く
Sing your dreams, loud and clear,
一緒に さあ
Together, come on!
まだ見ぬ世界へと
To a world yet unseen,
キミを連れてくよ
We'll take you there!
準備はほら出来たよ
Look, preparations are complete!
ルートも先回ったよ
We've mapped out the route ahead!
みんなが繋がる
A story where everyone connects,
物語 さあ始まるよ
It's starting now!
時は2026年！
The year is 2026!
2回目の3期生ライブ！
The second 3rd Generation Live!
このチャンスを逃してなるものか！
We won't let this chance slip away!
今こそ全人類
Now is the time...
兎化計画を遂行する！
To execute the Human Rabbit-ification Plan!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!